<resources>
    <string name="main_title"/>
    <string name="main_greeting" />
    <string name="start_gvl_button">Fotoüberweisung Starten</string>
    <string name="gini_capture_description">Gini Capture SDK</string>
    <string name="gini_pay_photopay_description">Gini Pay Photopay</string>
    
    <string name="gv_file_import_section_2_body"><![CDATA[To forward the file to Gini Pay FÜ app, use a function like "Open with...", "Send file..." or "Share" that is available within the app.\n\nThe "Share" function is often represented by an icon depicting a graph of three dots that are connected by two lines. These functions are often found in the overflow menu (three dots in the upper right corner of the screen) or in the function bar at the bottom edge of the app. In some email apps, the function is located near the PDF attachment before opening the file.]]></string>
    <string name="gv_file_import_section_3_title"><![CDATA[Select the Gini Pay FÜ app as the destination]]></string>
    <string name="gv_file_import_section_3_body"><![CDATA[When using this function, apps are shown to which you can send the PDF document. Please select the Gini Pay FÜ app from the list, to start the analysis and payment process.]]></string>
    <string name="gv_file_import_section_3_body_2"><![CDATA[Please use the option \"JUST ONCE\" to prevent the Gini Pay FÜ app from opening every PDF by default.]]></string>
    <string name="gv_file_import_section_3_clear_app_defaults_title">Clear app defaults</string>
    <string name="gv_file_import_section_3_clear_app_defaults_body"><![CDATA[In case you notice that Gini Pay FÜ opens every PDF by default, then you need to clear the app\'s “Open by default” settings:\n\n1. Open the Settings app.\n\n2. Tap “Apps & notifications”.\n\n3. Tap Gini Pay FÜ. If you don\'t see it, first tap “See all apps” or “App info”.\n\n4. Tap “Advanced” > “Open by default” > “Clear defaults”. If you don\'t see “Advanced”, tap “Open by default” > “Clear defaults”\n\nAfter clearing the default, when you open a PDF again, your device will ask you which app to use.]]></string>
</resources>

